Simon Fraser collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Fraser family artifacts, [19--] - 1995; F-208-4; 2 cm of textual records 2 drawings 4 artifacts 2 textiles
  - Artifact correspondence, vol. 1, 1964 - 1995; F-208-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 208-1)
  - Artifact correspondence, vol. 2, 1964 - 1995; F-208-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 208-1)